♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return to Wes Anderson's
Pan Up, Pan Down,
French Song, The End.
♪ Viens, suis-moi ♪
♪ Je connais une route... ♪
Wow, that was amazing, I think!
All right, everyone,
it's time to open up
our bank statements.
Let's gather
'round for prayer.
Hey, God, it's the Griffins.
Again, we're very sorry
we cyber-bullied
that girl to death.
But we still want a snowmobile.
Today, though,
please let there be money
in our bank account.
Amen. Amen.
Damn it.
It didn't work.
We're still poor.
Peter, every month our savings
get smaller and smaller.
We really gotta
figure out a better way
to budget for this
family's future.
Bitcoin.
What?
I don't know.
This is serious.
We need to think
about our kids' education.
Of course, it's already too late
for Meg to go to college.
And Chris is too dumb
to get in anywhere.
Yay!
No, Chris.
Not yay.
But there's still
time for Stewie.
Let's sit down later
and see if we can figure out
a plan to get our
finances in order.
Eh, don't worry
about it, Lois.
I will always provide
for the family.
Even if I have to
shoot our dinner.
This will look great
in my study.
I'm a hunter,
but I'm a silly hunter.
Hey, don't fill up on that.
We got breakfast coming.
Hey, Peter, I think
I figured out one way
we can save money
for Stewie's college.
If we bundle our cable
and Internet together,
we can save
$14 a month.
No! Bundling is
a sign of defeat!
Plus, I figured out
something better.
A metal detector.
What?
Yeah, it combines two of
America's greatest resources:
garbage and luck.
That's stupid,
Peter.
Ah, you're just
saying that
because the battery it uses
causes bladder cancer.
Well, then, I'm off.
I shall be at the beach
looking for valuables
and occasionally using
a doorless bathroom.
Good day, madam.
We now return to
The Awkward Stepdad Show.
Man, your mom's
a real groaner.
Do you hear that
in your room?
Hey, Dad,
where are you going?
Well, Meg, now that
I'm a metal detector guy,
I gotta start eating breakfast
at on-the-sand cafes,
where I will
judge tourists
as my skin browns
and hardens.
Stop throwin' your kid's diapers
in the trash
with all the soda cans!
Hey, Lois, check out what
I found with my metal detector.
Are those... are
those Purple Hearts?
Yeah, some idiot buried,
like, a hundred of 'em
in this big lawn
under these bone cages.
Peter!
I think you desecrated
a military graveyard!
Hey, guys, like four jeeps
just drove up
onto our front yard.
They must be here
for the medals!
Maybe. Or it could be
because of my
"I'm Gonna Barf
on the White House" blog.
Ah, sweet!
Huh.
Wonder what happens if I turn it
on and point 'em at each other.
Oh, my God!
Did you also call
into a talk show
without turning down
your radio first?
Jackpot.
Wow, an iPad!
This thing finds
everything!
Engagement ring!
Family locket!
Sunglasses that are an upgrade
- over my current pair!
- There he is!
There's the guy who's been
stealing everyone's stuff!
Don't yell at me,
I'm very sunburned!
Go, crappy car, go!
Peter, did you rob
a bunch of people
on the beach
with your metal detector?
Well, that's only
half the story.
I also hooted at a lady
who was breastfeeding.
I want you to get rid of
that metal detector.
All you're doing is
getting into trouble
and digging up junk
when we really need
to be saving
for Stewie's college.
Tomorrow we are
going to the mall
and returning that
thing to the store.
Okay, fine.
But you should know, the day
I bought this metal detector
was the happiest
day of my life.
Well, obviously,
the second happiest.
♪ Now we gonna do this thing
a little different tonight ♪
♪ You gonna come over,
pick me up in your ride ♪
Oh, my God, I wasn't even
supposed to be here.
I passed out at the Tom Petty
concert last night
and just stayed.
♪ You're gonna open my door ♪
♪ And I'm gonna reach over
and open yours ♪
♪ Gonna pay for dinner,
take me to see a movie ♪
♪ And whisper in my ear how bad
you really want to do me... ♪
Please, go slow.
I have IBS.
Well, I'm glad
the store was willing
to take that
metal detector back.
All right, let's go
to the food court.
I love eating
Panda Express
while squeezin' our purchases
between our knees
'cause someone
might grab 'em.
God, the mall sucks,
doesn't it, kids?
If I had a credit card,
I'd shop online.
Oh, hey, Bonnie.
What are you guys
doing here?
Oh, hey, Lois.
We saw an ad
looking for a toddler
to appear in a peanut
butter commercial
and we thought
we'd bring Susie.
Joe, are you wearing a corsage?
Yeah.
You can get a really good deal
on them after prom season.
They're for girls, Joe.
Hey, Peter,
why don't you let me do me,
and you do you, okay?
Peanut butter commercial, huh?
Hey, Bri, maybe
you should audition.
You know, because of that
one time you got in the trash
and ate a whole jar of
recalled peanut butter?
It wasn't peanut butter.
It was that pre-mixed peanut
butter and jelly thing.
Oh, Mom bought that?
That's what the scab kid
at school always has!
That was really great, Jake.
Really, really great.
Your face is upside-down,
so we're not gonna pick you,
but thanks for coming.
Hey. Hey.
This is you.
"I'm Brian.
"I like garbage
peanut butter,
and I wear my 'I Voted' sticker
for a week and a half."
Num-num-num-num-num-
num-num-num-num!
I'm sorry, we're looking for
more of a
"Num-num-num-num-num-num-num."
Bob, look over there!
Num-num-num-num-num-num-num-num-
num-num-num-num-num!
Whose kid is that?
Oh, that's our son, Stewie.
He's adorable!
And exactly what
we're looking for!
Congratulations, your son
is the new peanut butter kid!
My God, I don't believe it!
That's so cool!
Hey, what's Dad doing
over there with Chris?
Oh, he's telling him that he's
no longer his favorite son.
No!
No, Daddy!
Daddy!
Daddy...
I didn't even tell him.
He just does not
like to be touched.
Thanks for coming
to the viewing party
for Stewie's commercial,
everybody.
We're sorry that it's
airing during 2 Broke Girls,
but we have no
control over that.
Thanks for coming to
my big night, Brian.
I see you got all dressed up
in your exposed wiener.
Quiet, everybody!
Here it comes!
Welcome home, honey!
There's my family!
H-Hey, wait,
where's the baby?
Well, he likes
his hero dad,
but he loves
Scooter's Peanut Butter.
Num-num-num-num-num-num-num-num-
num-num-num-num-num-num-num!
Scooter's Peanut Butter.
So good, your baby
will want to eat it
in an airport terminal
bathroom.
He's a baby
who did a baby thing.
Let's all calm down
a little.
Wow, I can't believe
Stewie's a commercial star.
We haven't had a
celebrity in the family
since my great-aunt,
Queen of Burlesque Griffin.
♪ Cheesy jokes ♪
♪ And ugly broads ♪
♪ Way back when ♪
♪ They had no porn ♪
♪ Just scarves ♪
♪ Fans ♪
♪ Fat ♪
♪ Gross ♪
♪ A terrible time ♪
♪ For your penis to live in... ♪
Bill. Bill. Bill.
Weird magazine about
our town that's just ads.
Hmm, this one's for Stewie.
Whoa, a check for $2,000?
Let me see that.
It's a royalty check
from Stewie's commercial.
Apparently, he gets paid
every time it airs.
This is great.
We can put it right into
Stewie's college fund.
Yeah, yeah,
but, you know,
maybe we should keep
a little bit out to celebrate.
I mean, I ain't
done nothin' fancy
since I bought
those rich guy socks.
Ah, there.
I'm ready to get caught
cheating with my secretary.
♪ ♪
Welcome, folks.
Would you like flat
or sparkling water to start?
Garden hose
will be fine.
We prefer it to be hot
and then metal-y.
Actually, Peter,
let's go for the
sparkling water.
I mean, we are
celebrating
our little commercial
star and his big payday.
Oh, I don't care
about that, ma'am.
You know, this is
a nice dinner and all,
but I thought you guys
were going to save
this commercial money
for Stewie's college fund.
We are saving it, Brian.
This is just
a little celebration.
The rest of it is going
right in the bank.
Yeah, and besides,
it's been a while
since we ate at a place
where if you ask for ketchup,
they look at you
like you're dirt.
You know, Stewie
actually got a call
for another
commercial tomorrow.
Who knows?
This could be the beginning
of a nice career for him.
You sure about this, Lois?
I mean... I mean,
the world of child acting
can be a pretty bad
environment for a kid.
Maybe we should just
let Stewie's childhood
be about being a child.
Wasn't your kid an actor,
you jagoff?
Didn't your father
hate your guts and die?
Whoa!
Bring a gun to a knife fight.
Look, I-I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
All I'm saying is,
just try to keep Stewie's
best interests in mind.
Relax, Brian.
Stewie's fine.
I mean, look at him.
He's happier than
a sunny-side-up egg.
What a great way
to start the day.
What a pan, what a grill.
Oh no, I'm at Denny's.
Hey, I'm a drug addict
and it's midnight--
where's my breakfast?!
Help, he's only
gonna eat the toast
and put a cigarette out on me.
Okay, Stewie, you booked
the last commercial
without even trying, so this
one should be a piece of cake.
Oh, I guess there are other
people auditioning, too.
Oh, is your child up for the
cough syrup commercial, too?
You'd have no way
of knowing this,
but the moms tend
to dress up.
Oh, thank you.
And you'd have
no way of knowing
that my son is the
Scooter's Peanut Butter Kid.
That's cute.
My son had a gun waved in
his face in a Dexter episode.
Are you guys talking
about your kids?
My daughter is the American
Apparel slut baby.
My son got crapped on
in the last Jackass movie.
God, everyone here
is so talented.
Hi, everybody, we're
a little crunched for time,
so we're gonna have
to audition people
right here
in the hallway.
You, do something
exceptional.
Uh, okay.
Ow! Ow.
Oh, my grundle.
It's bruised.
It's bruised bad.
Oh, okay, I'm out, I'm out.
Tappin' out.
Well, that was
a disaster.
It was humiliating
is what it was.
That woman just smiled
when Stewie banged
his balls on the floor.
A damn disaster.
Num-num-num-num-num-
num-num-num-num?
Shut up,
that's over!
Did you see those other kids?
They were amazing.
One of them was texting
with the funny-dumb kid
from Modern Family.
I want to text with that kid.
Holy Christmas, there were
a lot of hot moms
in yoga pants in there though.
Dear me, they're really
disappointed in me, Rupert.
I haven't seen
the fat man this upset
since he went
to the 9/11 museum.
Lois made us do this,
but I wanted to go to the
Central Park merry-go-round.
We had time to do both!
What the hell?
♪ ♪
Okay, that's great, that's
great, that's great.
Just one question,
Stewie--
do you get pleasure out of
humiliating your family?
Yeah, is there some kind
of sick joy in it?
Why can't he just
be Pierce Brosnan?
Pierce Brosnan
would've got this.
In a heartbeat!
It's 3:00
in the morning.
What the hell
are you guys doing?
What does it look like?
We're practicing.
Stewie has another
audition tomorrow,
and we're not gonna be
embarrassed like we were today.
See, this is the kind
of thing I was talking about.
And look at him,
he can barely stand up.
That's why I made this--
I call it "8 Hour Energy."
It's one part 5-Hour Energy,
and the other three hours are
espresso, Scotts
Turf Builder,
and a tiny, tiny super-small
amount of cocaine.
Just a little bit.
I can't stress the
littleness of it enough.
Whoa, mama,
there's a kick like a mule!
♪ Who will buy
this wonderful morning ♪
♪ Such a sky
you never did see. ♪
There he is,
there's the magic.
Peter, you're giving
your baby drugs
to improve
his acting career?
Oh, he's fine
with it.
Stewie, if you're
fine with it,
bleed from the nose.
I think that's
pretty close.
All right, Stewie, now remember
what we practiced last night.
And here's a trick
to keep that confidence up.
You go in that room
and imagine everyone in it
wants you sexually.
I'm doing it right now,
and I feel powerful.
Okay.
And don't forget--
if you screw this up,
Mommy's gonna kill
all of your toys.
Okay.
All right, now I'm gonna go
psych out these other kids.
Hey, little guy.
Nervous?
Sure you are.
Here's something
that might help you.
Hey, little guy.
Stewie Griffin?
Oh, right here.
Peter, he
needs a boost.
Give him some of
the acting soup.
I want to say curse words!
Okay, Stewie, you're just
gonna drink this juice,
then say, "Mmm,"
and rub your belly.
Yeah, yeah,
you got it.
Yeah! Bye, juice!
That was amazing.
I've got goosebumps.
I want him
sexually.
Well, Mom, Dad,
I think we've got our
new orange juice boy.
Does this guy really
think we're his parents?
Stewie got the part?!
Yes!
That is how
you do it.
Oh, hey, Brian.
What's going on?
Where's the fridge?
Oh, we got a new one.
Stewie booked that
orange juice commercial,
so we thought we'd make a few
upgrades around the house.
Yeah, I even bought an awesome
voice-activated 3-D printer.
Why the hell do you
need a 3-D printer?
Print coyote.
Hey, what,
hey, no, no, no!
Heel, heel, heel!
I can't make him
attack you, Brian,
but if I keep
printing them,
eventually one will
go after you.
That money is supposed to
be for Stewie's college.
He's an actor, you idiot--
he doesn't need college.
Look, I-I just don't think any
of this is good for Stewie.
It's great for Stewie.
He's becoming a star.
That's right.
Man, this must be what it's like
to be Anne Hathaway's parents.
Oh, that's Anne's car.
Ugh.
Hey, Stewie, can
I talk to you?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
Mom and Dad just, uh, stuck
a book on my head and-and left.
Stewie, look at you,
you're a wreck.
And for what? So Peter and Lois
can spend the money you earned
on crap they
don't even need?
Uh, I'm not supposed
to use my voice
for non-paying
stuff, Brian.
This is insane--
you've got to stop.
Ugh, stop worrying,
I'm fine.
And besides, the fat man
knows what he's doing.
No, he doesn't,
he's an idiot.
Remember? He couldn't
even figure out
how to use a hotel
business center.
So what business
are you in?
Oh, I'm just here to look
at other people's e-mails
who haven't logged out.
And how's business?
Well, I've left some pretty wild
replies on a bunch of Evites.
Look at this-- I'm
bringing 53 guests.
You're the coolest guy I've ever
met in one of these things.
Oh, hey.
You caught me
pigging out.
I'm dipping this celery
stalk into some lemon water.
But don't freak out.
I'm just gonna smell it and
then throw it in the trash.
Stewie, this has
gotten out of control.
If you're gonna
continue on this path,
you need to know
what your future holds.
Being a child actor
almost never ends well.
You remember that kid
from A Christmas Story
who got his tongue
stuck to that pole?
Yeah, whatever
happened to him?
I'll tell you
what happened to him.
He did porn.
Boner from Growing Pains? Dead.
Screech from
Saved by the Bell? Porn.
Corey Haim? Dead.
Dana Plato? Porn, then dead.
Oh, no, this is horrible.
You see, Stewie, there are
tons of actors like this.
They all started out
just like you,
but eventually
they were destroyed
by their parents'
greed, drugs
or perverted
Hollywood directors.
Oh, like Bryan Singer.
Exactly. The point is
it's a dark path.
My God, I had no idea
it could be so bad.
Brian, I don't want
to act anymore.
Good. Now we just got to make
Peter and Lois understand.
Yes, well, if they want
to make me into a monster
like those people, we'll
give 'em a monster.
Like when Godzilla
attacked Haiti.
Oh, my God.
Peter, did you
get my text?
No, hold on.
No, I don't know
what he's doing here.
Okay, Stewie, when Barbara
hands you that orange juice,
you're gonna drink it
and smile.
And really show us that
energy from your audition.
H-Hold on a second,
he's got a smudge on his face.
Let me just take care
of that for you guys.
Here, drink this.
I threw a little Molly
in there, too,
so we'll go out
clubbing afterwards.
Hey, you want this?
Sure, I'll
drink anything.
All right, action!
As a mom, I want my kids
to start their day right.
And there's no better way
than with a glass
of fresh-squeezed
Sunnydale Orange Juice.
Isn't that right,
sweetie?
Shut your hole, bitch!
I'll tell you what I want
fresh-squeezed-- these.
What the hell's
he doing?
He's blowing this.
Oh, here's what I think
of this orange juice.
I-I can't... I can't go right
now with everybody watching.
But-but I presume you understand
the disrespect I intended.
Oh, my God, he's
having a meltdown.
You don't suppose this
has anything to do
with the sleep deprivation
and narcotics?
Oh, Peter, what have
we been thinking?
It's us-- we're the ones
who turned him into this.
Get this kid out of here!
He's fired.
Well done.
Not a bad performance.
Thank you, Brian, I...
Uh, there's the poop.
Right now.
Oh, Stewie.
Mommy and Daddy
are so sorry.
I-I guess we just got
too caught up in your success
and forgot that you're
just a baby.
You were
right, Brian.
I guess we pushed Stewie
a little too hard.
Well, the good news is
that now he can go back
to being a regular kid.
♪ ♪
Why are you winking at
our baby, you creep?
God, that's weird.
I don't want to ever
see that happen again.
Well, we went a little crazy
there, didn't we, Peter?
But I'm glad we have
our normal, very average,
non-famous baby back.
You know, I was once
a very famous baby.
Were you, Peter?
No, but you see how easy
it is for me to lie to you?
I do it every day.
Anyway, looks like everything
worked out for the best.
You know, Brian, that acting
stuff was a bit much for me,
but I did quite enjoy
the dancing and the cocaine.
Yeah?
Yep.
So you're just gonna be a
dancer and a drug addict?
For a while. I might
crash when I'm 18,
but then I'll just turn
to the Lord and working out.
I'll-I'll just be a 180 degree
different type of insufferable.
I used to need drugs
to feel powerful,
but now my power comes
from my core strength.
And let's look at that
word, "strength."
The "S" stands
for sacrifice.
No gain without
sacrifice.
The "T," of course, stands for
the sufferings of the cross.
The "R"...
You want some cocaine?
Oh, my God, please, yes!
That's all I want all the time!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru